Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 1157. Poems regarding interaction between friends, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1157)
  Side A. Tawfi?q Ibn Sa?i?d al-S?a?lih? reads many poems regarding interaction between friends.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker reads chapters on communications with brothers and friends.
  ????? ?????. ???? ????? ??? ???? ?????? ??? ????? ??? ??????? ?? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ??? ??? ??????? ??? ???? ?? ?????? ??? ?????? ? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1158. The reality of the Muslim nation, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1158)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture regarding the reality of the Muslim nation and the remoteness from religion.
  Side B. The International Symposium of Muslim Youth presented Dr ?Abd al-Rah?ma?n ibn S?a?lih? al-?Ashma?wi? who reads many poems regarding the pain and the reality of the Muslim nation. Note: please note that side B is the beginning of the audiotape.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ???? ????? ????????? ? ????? ?? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ?????? ??????? ?????? ??????? ??? ?????? ??? ???? ???????? ???? ???? ????? ?? ???? ????? ?????????. ??????: ????? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1159. Asceticism, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1159)
  Side A. A speaker reads poems regarding about asceticism.
  Side B. A speaker reads poems regarding about asceticism.
  ????? ?????. ????? ?? ?????
  ????? ??????. ????? ?? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1160. Asceticism, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1160)
  Side A. [Duplicate of Tape 1159, Side A].
  Side B. [Duplicate of Tape 1159, Side B].
  ????? ?????. [?????? ??? 1159, ????? ????? ???].
  ????? ??????. [?????? ??? 1159, ????? ?????? ???].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1161. Asceticism, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1161)
  ????? ??????. ????? ?? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1162. Poems about Jihad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1162)
  Side A. Dr Yu?suf Muh?yi? al-Di?n Abu? Hila?lah and others read poems about Jihad and famine in Ethiopia. At the end of the audio tape, a speaker urges the audience to donate money for Jihad. Note: This audio tape was recorded in Riyad ( Saudia Arabia)
  Side B. The audio tape starts with the sound of rockets. Continuation to side A. Dr Za?hir ?Awwa?d? al-Alma?i?, Yu?suf Muh?yi? al-Di?n Abu? Hila?lah and Dr ?Abd al-Rah?ma?n al-?Ashma?wi? read many poems regarding Jihad.
  ????? ?????. ???? ??????? ? ???? ??? ????? ??? ????? ? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ??????? ?? ???????. ?? ??? ?????? ??????, ?? ????? ??? ????????? ??? ?????? ??????. ??????: ??? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?? ??????
  ????? ??????. ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ???????. ???? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????. ??? ??????? ???? ???? ??????? ? ???? ??? ????? ??? ????? ? ??? ?????? ???????? ????? ?? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1164. The media committee of al-Qa??idah, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1164)
  Side A. The media committee of al-Qa??idah presented a wedding ceremony for one of the Mujahedeen member (named ?Umar ?A?s?im). Many speakers present poems regarding Jihad and marriage and answer questions regarding the relationship between al-Qa??idah and the United States. One of the poems, "Dangerous Terrorist", was dedicated to Sheikh Usa?mah ibn La?din.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The presenter of the wedding ceremony states that al-Sharq al-Awsat? newspaper mentions in an article that Sheikh Usa?mah ibn La?din founded a country called Jihadstan, which is country without borders and without population.
  ????? ?????. ???? ?????? ????????? ??????? ??? ??? ??? ????????? { ???? ??? ????}. ?????? ??? ?????? ? ?????? ?????? ??????? ????????? ???????. ???? ??????? ???? ?????? " ?????? ????" ???? ????? ????? ????? ?? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ??? ???? ????? " ??? ????? ????? ?????? ???? ?? ??? ??????? ??? ????? ????? ?? ???? ??? ???? ???? ????????, ??? ??? ???? "
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1165. Conversation with a Jinni, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1165)
  Side A. A conversation with a Jinni (Russian converted to Islam) who answers questions regarding the Mujahedeen leaders.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The Jinni states that the Arabs do not know how to plan and Iran must be Iran; he also states that the Arabs and Muslims do not know how to plan.
  ????? ?????. ???? ?? ??? { ???? ????? ???????} ??? ???? ?? ????? ????? ??????? ?????????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ??? ????? ??? "????? ??? ??????, ??? ??? ??? ?????? ?????" ???? ??? ????? ?? ?????? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1166. Jihad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1166)
  Side A. The Audiotape starts with the sound of bombs and rockets. The speaker uses a language other than Arabic; some Arabic words were mentioned, such as Islam and Jihad.
  Side B. The Audiotape starts with the sound of bombs and rockets. The speaker uses a language other than Arabic; some Arabic words were mentioned, such as life, Jihad, and America.
  ????? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ??????? ?????????. ?? ???? ???? ??? ????? ? ???? ??? ??????? ??????? ??? ??????? ???????.
  ????? ?????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ??????? ?????????. ??? ??? ????? ? ??? ??????? ??????? ???? ??? ?????? ? ?????? ? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1167. Jihad, Circa 1965-1999; 1 (Box 1167)
  Side A. The audio tape starts with the sound of the bombs and rockets. The speaker uses an unidentifiable language; some Arabic words were mentioned, such as Islam and Jihad.
  Side B. The audio tape starts with the sound of the bombs and rockets. The speaker uses an unidentifiable language; some Arabic words were mentioned, such as life, Jihad, and America.
  ????? ????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ??????? ?????????. ??? ??? ?????? ? ??? ??????? ??????? ???? ??? ??????? ???????.
  ????? ?????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ??????? ?????????. ??? ??? ?????? ? ??? ??????? ??????? ???? ??? ?????? ? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1168. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1168)
  Side A. Interpretation of some Quranic verses in an unidentified language.
  Side B. Interpretation of some Quranic verses in an unidentified language.
  ????? ?????. ????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1169. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1169)
  Side A. An unidentified language.
  Side B. An unidentified language.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ???? ??? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1170. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1170)
  ????? ?????. ?????? ???? ??? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1171. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1171)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1172. Jihad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1172)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture regarding Jihad in An unidentified language. Note: the speaker mentions a Hadith regarding Jihad in Arabic.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture regarding Jihad in An unidentified language. Note: the speaker mentions a Hadith regarding Jihad in Arabic.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ???? ??? ????? ?? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ???? ??? ????? ?? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies
- Tape 1173. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1173)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture in an unidentified language.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture in an unidentified language.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1174. Multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1174)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on multiple topics in which he discusses Hajj as an international Islamic conference and the Masonic rule in the Muslim countries.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture on multiple topics in which he discusses Jihad and boycotts. Another speaker recites from the Qur'an 45:24-37 and 46:1-26.
  ????? ?????. ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ??? ??????, ??? ???? ???? ? ??? ??? ???? ????? ????? ???? ?????? ? ??? ????????? ?? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ?????? ?????? ????????, ? ????? ?????? ? ????????, ?? ????? ????? ?? ????? ??????? ? ???????".
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1175. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1175)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture in a language other than Arabic. From minute 12, a recording of an Islamic anthem regarding the love for the Prophet Mohammed.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ???? ??? ?????, ?? ??????? 12 ?????? ??????? ?? ?? ??????.
  ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1176. ?am?s, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1176)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture in unidentified language.
  Side B. A series of Mujahedeen recite anthems regarding ?am?s (Islamic Resistance Movement). Another speaker gives a lecture in a language other than Arabic.
  ????? ??????. ???? ?????? ????????? ?????? ?? ???? ????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1177. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1177)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1178. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1178)
  Side A. A speaker interprets some Qur'anic verses in an unidentified language.
  Side B. A speaker interprets some Qur'anic verses in an unidentified language.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1179. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1179)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1180. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1180)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1181. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1181)
  ????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1182. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1182)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1183. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1183)
  ???? ??????. ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1184. Unidentified language, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1184)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture regarding Jihad in an unidentified language.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture regarding Jihad in an unidentified language.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??? ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ??? ?????? ???? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1185. English lessons, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1185)
  Side A. New Intercom Company gives many English lessons.
  Side B. New Intercom Company gives many English lessons.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1186. English lessons, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1186)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1187. English lessons, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1187)
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1188. World War I and the fall of the Islamic Caliphate, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1188)
  Side A. An Egyptian speaker gives a lecture on the World War I and the fall of the Islamic Caliphate. The speaker discusses and answers questions regarding the role of the Jews, the Pope, and the Church in World War I.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker concentrates on the role of the United States in helping the Israel government.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??? ????? ???????? ?????? ? ???? ??????? ?????????, ? ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ??? ??? ?????? ? ?????? ? ??????? ???? ????? ???????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ??? ??? ??????? ??? ????????? ????????? ????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1189A. Multiple topics, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1189A)
  Side Aa. An Egyptian speaker gives a lecture on Ramadan. Many speakers read Islamic anthems.
  Side Ab. Sheikh Mus?t?afa? Isma??i?l recites from the Qur'an 11:61-78 and 14:34-41. Another speaker answers and discuses some issues regarding Ramadan.
  Side Ba. A speaker gives a lecture on the British invasion of Saudi Arabia
  Side Bb. Continuation to side Ba, the speaker concentrates on the Soviet Union in Afghanistan, the Islamic awakening, and World War II.
  ????? ??. ?????? ? ?????? ??? ??? ????? ??????? ????.
  ????? ? ?. ??? ????? ????? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ??????. ??? ???? ????? ??? ????? ??? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1189B. British invasion of Saudi Arabia, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1189B)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the British invasion of Saudi Arabia.
  Side B. Continuation to side A, the speaker concentrates on the Soviet Union in Afghanistan, the Islamic awakening, and World War II.
  ????? ? ?. ?????? ??? ????? ????????? ????????.
  ???? ? ?. ???? ????? ? ?, ??? ??? ??????? ??? ??????? ???????? ?? ????????? ? ?????? ????????? ??? ????? ???????? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1190. Arabic grammar, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1190)
  Side A. Lecture on Arabic grammar.
  Side B. Lecture on Arabic grammar.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??? ????? ????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ??? ????? ????? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1191. Unity of Yemen, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1191)
  Side A. A recording of a conference regarding the unity of Yemen in the presence of the president ?Ali? ?Abd Alla?h S?a?lih?, and other Yemeni scholars. The speakers and the president ?Ali? ?Abd Alla?h Sa?lih? discuss the unity of Yemen and the importance of building a strong society based on the idea of brotherhood that the Prophet Mohammed applied among Muslims in Madinah.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speakers commented on the president regarding the unity of Yemen and suggested that the new constitution must be based on the Islamic laws.
  ????? ?????. ????? ?? ?????? ?? ?????, ? ???? ?????? ?????? ??? ???? ?? ???? ?????? ?????? ?????? ??? ?????? ?? ????? ???????? ?? ????? ??????, ??? ??? ????? ???? ??? ???????? ?? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ??? ???? ?????? ?????? ???? ?????? ???????? ?? ???? ??????? ?????? ????? ??? ??????? ?????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1192. Interview with Dr Mohammed al-mus'ri, Circa 1994; 1 (Box 1192)
  Side A. An interview with Mohammed al-mus'ri regarding his imprisonment and how he was questioned in Saudi Arabia by government the authorities.
  Side B. A presenter introduces Mohammed al-Mus'ri who discusses his experience during imprisonment. Note: side B is the beginning of the Audiotape.
  ????? ?????. ???? ?? ???? ??????? ??? ???? ?? ???????? ? ????? ??????? ??? ?? ??? ??????? ????????.
  ????? ??????. ??? ?????? ?????? ?????? ??????? ???? ???????, ???? ???? ???? ???? ?? ????????. ??????: ????? ?????? ?? ????? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1193. Islamic anthems, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1193)
  Side A. Islamic anthems regarding the reality of Muslims and Jihad.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. Islamic anthems in an indentified language.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??????? ?? ? ???? ???????? ? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ?? ?????? ???? ??? ?????..
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1194. Islamic anthems, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1194)
  Side A. Islamic anthems regarding victory.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??????? ?? ?????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ??????? ?? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1195. Jihad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1195)
  Side A. Many speakers give speeches, Hadith, anthems and stories regarding Jihad.
  ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ? ?????? ???? ?? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1196. S?ala?h? al-Di?n al-Ayyu?bi?, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1196)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on S?ala?h? al-Di?n al-Ayyu?bi?, in which he discusses the improvement of the Muslim countries while he was ruling.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. the speaker concentrates on the manners of S?ala?h? al-Di?n al-Ayyu?bi?.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ???? ????? ???????, ??? ???? ??????? ???????? ???? ???? ?? ????? ????????? ?? ??? ???? ????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ??? ??? ??????? ??? ????? ???? ????? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1197. Interpretation of a Qur?a?nic, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1197)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the interpretation of the Qu'ranic verse "For to anything which we have willed, We but say the word, "Be", and it is."
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker mentions several example of God's greatness.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??? ??? ????? ??????? " ???????? ????????? ???????? ????? ??????????? ??? ???????? ???? ??? ?????????".
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ??? ??? ??????? ??? ????? ????? ????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1198. Jihadist member from Algeria, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1198)
  Side A. A Jihadist member from Algeria reads the platform of the organization in which he discusses the recruitment of youth and the assassination of figures in Algerian society Note: the speaker reads the numbered platform from article numbers 11 to 74.
  Side B. [Duplicate of Tape 1198, Side A].
  ????? ?????. ??? ??? ????????? ?? ??????? ???????? ??????? ???? ???? ??? ????? ?????? ??????? ???????? ?? ??????? ????????.
  ????? ??????. [??? ?????? ?????? ???1198, ????? ?????].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1199. Interview with Usa?mah ibn La?din, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1199)
  Side A. A French journalist interviews Usa?mah ibn La?din and asks questions regarding the role of the Sa'udi Royal family in helping Usa?mah ibn La?din..
  Side B. Usa?mah ibn La?din answers questions regarding the Taliban, the Islamic awakening, and American politics.
  ????? ?????. ???? ???? ????? ???? ?? ????? ?? ???? ??? ???? ?? ????? ?? ???? ????????? ?????? ?? ????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?? ???? ??? ????? ????? ????? ?????? ? ?????? ????????? ? ??????? ?????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1200. The meaning of Faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1200)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the meaning of faith to a Sunni group and teaches the pronunciation of some words in the Arabic language.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker discusses the Syriac language and how it is close to the Arabic language.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ??? ???? ??????? ??? ??? ????? ? ????? ??? ??? ??????? ?? ????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????????? ?? ????? ???????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1201. Destiny and fate, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1201)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on destiny and fate.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker concentrates on the meaning of faith and destiny according to the Sunnis.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ?????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ??????. ??? ??? ??????? ??? ???? ??????? ??? ??? ?????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1202. Death, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1202)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on death, in which he discusses verses from the Qur'an to remind people of death and to work for life hereafter.
  Side B. A speaker gives a lecture on multiple topics, in which he mentions the life of Sayyid Qut?b.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ???? ?????? { ?????}, ??? ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ?????? ? ????? ?????? ?????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ?????? ?? ??? ??????, ???? ??? ????? ???.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1203. Women veil, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1203)
  Side A. A speaker gives a sermon on women's veils. Another speaker gives a lecture on women, the veil, and ancestral stories.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker concentrates on women's veils.
  ?????? ?? ???? ??????, ? ??? ?? ????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1204. The Muslims history in Spain, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1204)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on The Muslims history in Spain.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker states that the selfishness on the part of Muslims is the cause of the fall of Spain. A young boy recites from the Qur'an 29:28-40.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ????? ???????? ?? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ??? ??????? ???" ?????? ???????? ?? ???? ??? ??? ???? ???????". ??? ??? ??? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1205. Jihad, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1205)
  Side A. A speaker gives a sermon about the fear shown by Israelis soldiers because of Palestinians throwing rocks.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. In the second sermon, the speaker mentions a statement from the Eritrean Jihad movement.
  ????? ?????. ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ???????????? ?? ????? ???????????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????. ???? ?? ???? ?????? ????????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1206. Yemen unity, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1206)
  Side A. Sheikh ?Abd al-Maji?d al-Zanda?ni? gives a lecture on Yemeni unity and applying God's laws.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker states that the Israelis and the Americans are afraid of Islam and the Mujahedeen. The speaker also concentrates on Yemeni unity in the North and South.
  ????? ?????. ???? ????? ??? ?????? ???????? ?????? ??? ?????? ??????? ? ????? ??????? ?????????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ??? ??? ????? ??? ?????? ???????? ??? " ???????????? ? ?????????? ?????? ?? ??????? ? ??????", ? ??? ??????? ??? ?????? ??????? ?? ?????? ? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1207. The situations of the Arab countries, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1207)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the situation of citizens in Arab countries.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. Another speaker recites from the Qur'an 25:1-7.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ??? ???????? ?? ????? ???????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ??? ???? ??? ???? ?? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1208. The conditions of divorce, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1208)
  Side A. A speaker gives a lecture on the conditions of divorce, in which he discusses the viewpoint of Muslim scholars. The speaker states that the Muh?allil (a person who marries a divorced woman, in order to go back to her previous husband) is not valid.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker concentrates on the Muh?allil. Another speaker recites from the Qur'an 2:228-260.
  ????? ?????. ?????? ?? ???? ??????, ??? ???? ??????? ???? ??? ??????? ?? ???? ???? " ??????" ? ????? ??? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ???? ????? ?????, ? ??? ??????? ??? ????? " ??????", ?? ??? ???? ???? ?? ???? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1209. Recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1209)
  Side A. Twafiq Salah recites from the Qur'an 37:105-182, 38:1-88 and 39:1-75.
  Side B. Twafiq Salah recites from the Qur'an 34:1-54, 35:1-45 and 36:1-76.
  ????? ?????. ????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???? ????? ????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1210. Recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1210)
  Side A. A speaker recites from the Qur'an from Surat 43 to Surat number 47.
  Side B. Continuation to side A. The speaker recites Surat 47 to 53.
  ????? ?????. ????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ??????.
  ????? ??????. ????? ???? ????? ?? ?????? ??????.
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 1211. Recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 1211)
  Side A. A speaker recites from the Qur'an Surat 10 and 11.
  Side B. A speaker recites from the Qu'ran Surat 9 and 10. Note: please note that side B is the beginning of the Audio tape.